### KORINNA ASSING

Plainsboro, NJ

Phone: 908-590-1786 | Email: kaassing@gmail.com

LinkedIn: LinkedIn.com/in/korinnaassing | GitHub: github.com/kassing3 |

Portfolio: bit.ly/KorinnaPortfolio

### SUMMARY

A user-centered Full-Stack Developer with a strong project management background. Skillful in designing, programming, and debugging responsive web applications that enhance user experiences and meet business objectives. A multilingual and multifaceted developer with experience in React.js, Python, MongoDB, Express, Node, Git, and various programming languages and methods.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages & Methods: Affinity Mapping, Bootstrap, CSS, Express.js, Git, GraphQL, Handlebars.js, HTML, JavaScript, Jest, jQuery, MongoDB, MySQL, Node.js, Python, React.js, Sequalize Applications: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD, Figma, GitHub, Heroku, Insomnia, Jira, Miro, Slack, Visual Studio Code, WordPress, Zoom

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Project Manager - Senior Air Partnership Associate Intersection**

Nov. 2021 – Current New York, NY

- Engineer a transit authority monthly reporting dashboard in Tableau using Figma and SQL for design and software development, which resulted in winning the Automagic Award for Intersection's Hackathon event and increasing productivity among internal teams and partners
- Cultivate cohesive relationships between four major air partners and internal cross-functional teams by spearheading projects through a combination of agile and waterfall methodologies
- Significantly increase productivity and revenue across the Air market by conducting user research to design and engineer transformative process tools and project trackers

# **Lead Sales Coordinator** (Promoted twice from Sales Coordinator) **Intersection**

Dec. 2017 – Oct. 2021 Philadelphia, PA

- Directed a high-performing team of Sales Coordinators by facilitating the interview and onboarding processes for new hires and conducting training, team meetings, weekly one-on-ones, and quarterly performance reviews
- Successfully orchestrated the sale lifecycle of deals by building a supreme rhythmic business flow between cross-functional teams and clientele, delivering on-time execution of projects to meet critical goals of campaign launches, and partnering on strategies to achieve revenue goals
- Aligned with NRG and the internal Account Executive team to accumulate research data on the target customer and KPIs and solidify a 5-year NRG Naming Rights Deal that generated over \$5M and produced over 200 million impressions annually
- Partnered with Sales and Marketing teams to create high-impact sponsorship proposals and strategies for PECO, resulting in over \$8M in revenue and 400M impressions annually

### AMERICORPS Sustainability Project Coordinator Sustainability Department, City of Newark

Jun. 2017 – Nov. 2017 Newark, NJ

 Formalized the implementation of green infrastructure and disaster preparedness projects by partnering with City Officials and stakeholders to coordinate five workshops for environmental health and quality of life issues

- Collaborated with the Chief of Sustainability and key stakeholders to create sustainable contingency plans to mitigate environmental community risks such as extreme heat, flooding, and fresh air that resulted in a 20% savings and was delivered five months ahead of schedule
- Crafted education and marketing materials with the Communications team to increase web traffic by 10% and resident attendance to programs by 25%
- Engaged residents and community members to facilitate and empower Impact Volunteering initiates that increased awareness of the City of Newark's resources and expanded the city's network of volunteers

# Marketing Coordinator/Photographer Recreation Department - Rutgers University

May 2016 – May 2017 New Brunswick, NJ

- Programmed social media and web content and performed social media analysis to calculate quantitative reports
- Initiated the "RU Trailblazing Thursday" campaign, highlighting the success of sport club teams to the Big 10 Community
- Designed marketing materials for social media, print, and web applications with the use of Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, and Adobe Lightroom

#### **EDUCATION**

Full-Stack Coding Boot Camp Certificate: Rutgers University-New Brunswick, NJ

**Google IT Automation with Python** 

**Google UX Design Certificate** 

Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM)®

B.S. Communication: Rutgers University-New Brunswick, NJ

Adobe Photoshop Certificate in CS6 & CS5

### **P**ROJECTS

### Stacks | bit.ly/StacksCaseStudy

- **Summary:** A case study for a financial literacy app that targets young adults based on UX Research to define users' needs and ideate efficient designs to prototype and test web and mobile applications
- Role: UX Researcher/ Designer
- Tools: Figma, Adobe XD, SurveyMonkey, Jamboard

### ShelfLife https://github.com/marchocobar/fantastic-octo-enigma

- Summary: A digital bookshelf that allows users to search and save their favorite books
- Role: Full Stack Developer
- Tools: MongoDB, Express, Node, Git, Node.js, Heroku, React.js

### Binge https://github.com/marchocobar/Movie-Database-P1G7

- **Summary:** A movie companion web application that allows users to search and save their favorite or must-watch movies for future viewing
- **Role:** Frontend Developer
- Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, API, Bulma